Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Rice Sports (see also Series I: Swimming records), 1941-2004 (Boxes 46-71), 201056
  - Subseries D: Football, 1941-1998, 201119
    - 1982 Southwestern LA, 201235 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 1982 TCU, 201234 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - 1982 Texas, 201233 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - 1982 Texas A and M, 201232 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - 1982 Texas Tech, 201231 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - 1982 Tulane, 201230 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - 1982 USL, 201229 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - 1982 UT, 201228 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - 1983, 201227 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - 1983 "Greater Houston Football Magazine", 201226 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - 1983 Play-by-plays, 201225 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - 1983 Arkansas, 201224 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - 1983 Baylor, 201223 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - 1983 Houston, 201222 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - 1983 Khiva Shrine Bowl, 201221 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - 1983 LSU, 201220 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - 1983 Minnesota, 201219 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - 1983 SMU, 201218 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - 1983 SW Louisiana, 201217 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - 1983 TCU, 201216 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - 1983 Texas, 201215 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - 1983 Texas A and M, 201214 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - 1983 Texas Tech, 201213 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - 1983 USL, 201212 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - 1983 UT vs. Texas A and M, 201211 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - 1983-84 Sports News, 201210 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - 1984, 201209 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - 1984 Fact Sheets, 201208 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - 1984 SWC, 201207 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 1985, 201206 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 1985 Folder 2, 201205 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 1985 Folder 3, 201204 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 1985 Newcomers, 201203 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 1985 Rice Owls Game Notes, 201202 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 1985 Blue Bonnet Bowl (Air Force vs Texas), 201201 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 1986, 201200 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - 1986 Baylor, 201199 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - 1986 Houston, 201198 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - 1986 Lamar, 201197 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - 1986 Southwest Texas, 201196 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - 1986 Texas, 201195 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - 1986 Texas A and M, 201194 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - 1986-87 Blue Bonnet Bowl, 201193 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - 1987, 201192 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - 1987-88 Expenses, 201191 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - 1987 Arkansas, 201190 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - 1987 Houston - Home, 201189 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - 1987 Indiana, 201188 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - 1987 Indiana - Away, 201187 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - 1987 Lamar, 201186 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - 1987 LSU, 201185 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - 1987 SW Texas State, 201184 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - 1987 TCU, 201183 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - 1987 Texas - Away, 201182 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - 1987 Texas A and M, 201181 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - 1987 Texas Tech, 201180 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - 1988 Photos, 201179 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - 1988 Rice Owls, 201178 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Stat Forms, 201177 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Baylor, 201176 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Indiana, 201175 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1988 N Texas State - Home, 201174 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Texas - Home, 201173 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Texas Tech - Home, 201172 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - 1989-90 Rice Owls, 201171 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - 1989, 201170 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - 1989 Photos, 201169 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - 1989 Scoring Summary, 201168 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - 1989 Arkansas, 201167 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - 1989 Baylor, 201166 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - 1989 Houston, 201165 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - 1989 SMU, 201164 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - 1989 TCU, 201163 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - 1989 Texas, 201162 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - 1989 Texas A and M, 201161 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - 1989 Texas Tech, 201160 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - 1989 Tulane, 201159 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - 1989 USL, 201158 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - 1989 Wake Forest, 201157 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - 1990, 201156 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - 1990 Arkansas, 201155 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - 1990 Baylor, 201154 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - 1990 Northwestern, 201153 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - 1990 SMU, 201152 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - 1990 Texas, 201151 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - 1990 Texas Tech, 201150 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - 1990 Tulane, 201149 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - 1990 Wake Forest, 201148 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - 1990 Scoring Summary, 201147 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - 1991, 201146 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1991 Statistics, 201145 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - 1991 Publicity, 201144 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - 1992, 201143 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - 1992 Non-Game Material (includes Trevor Obb material), 201142 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - 1993 Scoring Summary, 201141 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - 1993, 201140 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - 1993 Recruiting, 201139 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - 1994, 201138 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - 1995, 201137 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - 1996, 201136 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - 1997, 201135 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - 1997-98, 201134 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - 1998, 201133 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Brochures, 201132 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Certificates, 201131 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Clippings; folder 1 of 3, 201130 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Clippings; folder 2 of 3, 201129 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Clippings; folder 3 of 3, 201128 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - General, 201127 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Photos, 201126 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Photos; beginning A. Brinkley, 201125 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Photos; beginning R. Askew, 201124 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Releases - General Stadium - Tickets, 201123 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Requests, 201122 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Team Travel, 201121 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Varsity Releases, 201120 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Subseries E: Tennis, 1985-2004, 201070
    - Women's Tennis 1985, 201118 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Women's Tennis Results, 201117 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Women's Tennis 1988, 201116 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Men's Tennis 1988, 201115 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Chris, 201114 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Ben, 201113 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Jon, 201112 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Nick, 201111 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Rico, 201110 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Peter, 201109 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Bert, 201108 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Von Heintze, 201107 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Shane, 201106 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Ryan Gately, 201105 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Jose Medrano, 201104 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Juan LaValle, 201103 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Matt Berry, 201102 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Justin Hogan, 201101 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - 1986 Tarek El Saha, 201100 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Pascal Hos, 201099 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Willie Dannin, 201098 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Steve Campbell, 201097 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Wayne Fauer, 201096 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Justin Reizes, 201095 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Certificates, 201094 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Clippings, 201093 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Photos, 201092 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco Trip, 201091 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Lights Construction, 201090 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Parker/Seewager at Harvard, 201089 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Rice Tennis Classic, 201088 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - 1990 NCAA, 201087 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - 1990 Reunion, 201086 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - 1990 Rice Invitational, 201085 (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - 1990 Team Shots, 201084 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - 1990 UT Conference Champs, 201083 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - 1991 America West, 201082 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - 1991 Day Camp and Club Champs, 201081 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Women's Tennis 1991 Media Guide, 201080 (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - 1991 NCAA, 201079 (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - 1991 Reunion, 201078 (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - 1991 Team Pinewood, 201077 (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Men's Tennis 1992, 201076 (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - 1992 America West, 201075 (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - 1992 Reunion, 201074 (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - 1992 Rice Invitational, 201073 (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - 1992 River Oaks, 201072 (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - 2004, 201071 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Subseries F: Volleyball, 1983-2001, 201060
    - 1983, 201069 (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - 1988, 201068 (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - 1990, 201067 (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 201066 (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - 1998 Scrapbook, 201065 (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - 1998 Newspaper Articles, 201064 (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - 2001 Statistics and Press Releases, 201063 (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Photos, 201062 (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - Clippings, 201061 (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Subseries G: Golf, 1988-1990, 201057
    - 1988, 201059 (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - 1990, 201058 (Box 71, Folder 59)
- Series IV: Photographs and Slides, 1912-2000s (Boxes 72-100), 200556
  Arrangement note
  Due to the size of this record group, materials are arranged by format first and then by sport.
  - Subseries A: Slides in Protective Sheets, 1950-2000s, 200963
    - Sub-subseries 1: Baseball, 1986-2000, 201046
      - Color Slides; 1986, 201055 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Color Slides; 1987, 201054 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Color Slides; 1988, 201053 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Color Slides; 1989, 201052 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Color Slides; 1994, 201051 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Color Slides; 1995, 201050 (Box 72, Folder 6-7)
      - Color Slides by T. Lavergne (College World Series); 1999, 201049 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Color Slides by T. Lavergne (outside stadium and at game); 2000, 201048 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Color Slides, 1990's, 201047 (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Men's Basketball, 1985-1996, 201037
      - Color Slides; 1985, 201045 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Color Slides; 1987-88, 201044 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides, 1988-91, 201043 (Box 72, Folder 14-15)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides, 1993, 201042 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Rice Mug Shots- Color Slides; 1993, 201041 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Color Slides; 1994, 201040 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1994-95, 201039 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1995-96, 201038 (Box 73, Folder 3-4)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Women's Basketball, 1985-2000, 201028
      - Color Slides; 1985, 201036 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Color Slides; 1986, 201035 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Color Slides; 1986-87, 201034 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1988-91, 201033 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 201032 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Color Slides; 1994, 201031 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1995-96, 201030 (Box 73, Folder 11-12)
      - NCAA Tournament Color Slides; 2000, 201029 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Cross Country Track, 1994-1995, 201026
      - Color Slides; 1994-95, 201027 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Football, ca.1950s-2000s, 201003
      - Black and white slides; pre 1970's, 201025 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Color Slides; 1984, 201024 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1987-1988, 201023 (Box 73, Folder 17-18)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides (Folders 1 and 2 of 3); 1988-89, 201022 (Box 73, Folder 19-20)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides (Folder 3 of 3); 1988-89, 201021 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1993, 201020 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Individual Rice Mug Shots- Color Slides; 1991, 201019 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Individual Rice Mug Shots- Color Slides; 1992, 201018 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Homecoming Game Color Slides; 1994, 201017 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1994, 201016 (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
      - Rice vs. Texas Tech- Cheerleaders- Color Slides; 1994, 201015 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1995, 201014 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Game and Individual Color Slides; 1996, 201013 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Cheerleaders Color Slides; 1980's-1990's, 201012 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Color Slides by T. Lavergne; 1980's-1990's, 201011 (Box 74, Folder 12-14)
      - Color Slides by T. Lavergne; 1999, 201010 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Color Slides-Tailgating by T. Lavergne; 2000, 201009 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Games-Color Slides; 1970's-2000's, 201008 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Rice Mug Shots- Color Slides; 1980-1990's, 201007 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Color Slides; 1980's-2000's, 201006 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Rice vs. Baylor-Color Slides; 1980's-2000's, 201005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Cox Lifting Room-Color Slides; 1980's-2000's, 201004 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 6: Men's Golf, 1993-1995, 201000
      - Color Slides; 1993-1994, 201002 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Color Slides; 1994-95, 201001 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Sub-subseries 7: Swimming, 1984-1995, 200996
      - Color Slides; 1984, 200999 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 200998 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Color Slides; 1994-95, 200997 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries 8: Men's Tennis, 1984-2000s, 200990
      - Color Slides; 1984, 200995 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Color Slides; 1986, 200994 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 200993 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Color Slides; 1994-95, 200992 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Color Slides; 1990's - 2000's, 200991 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Sub-subseries 9: Women's Tennis, 1984-2000s, 200986
      - Color Slides; 1984, 200989 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Color Slides; 1993, 200988 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Color Slides; 1990's - 2000's, 200987 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Sub-subseries 10: Men's and Women's Tennis, 1986-2000s, 200983
      - Color Slides; 1990's-2000's, 200985 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - Jake Hess Stadium- Color Slides; 1986, 200984 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Sub-subseries 11: Men's Track1993-1995, 200980
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 200982 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - Color Slides; 1994-95, 200981 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Sub-subseries 12: Women's Track, 1987-1994, 200977
      - Competition-Color Slides; 1987, 200979 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 200978 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries 13: Track and Field, 1985-2000s, 200972
      - Meet of Champions-Color Slides; 1985, 200976 (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - Color Slides; 1988, 200975 (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Color Slides; 1989, 200974 (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Color Slides; 1980's-2000's, 200973 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Sub-subseries 14: Assorted Sports, 1982-2000s, 200964
      - Color Slides; 1982-86, 200971 (Box 75, Folder 27-28)
      - Color Slides; 1984-86, 200970 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Campus Shots- Color Slides; 1970's-1980's, 200969 (Box 75, Folder 30)
      - Color Slides; 1993-94, 200968 (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - Color Slides; 1980's-2000's, 200967 (Box 75, Folder 32-33)
      - Duplicate Color Slides for Athletics Department; 1980's-2000's, 200966 (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Sports Shots- Color Slides; various years, 200965 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Subseries B: Photographs and Negatives, 1912-2000s, 200725
    - Sub-subseries 1: Baseball, 1923-2000s, 200947
      - Group and Team - Photographs; 1923, 200962 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Group and Team - Photos; pre1970's, 200961 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Games - Photos; pre 1970's, 200960 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Individual Shots - Photos; 1972, 200959 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Individual Shots - Photos; pre-1980s, 200958 (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
      - Coaches (Headshots) - Photos; pre 1980's, 200957 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Headshots - Photos and Negatives; 1990's, 200956 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Western Athletic Conference (WAC) Championship Booklet; 1998, 200955 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - WAC Champions - Photos and Negatives; 1998, 200954 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Individual Shots - Photos; 1970's-2000's, 200953 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Rice vs. UCLA - Games Negatives; 1908's -2000's, 200952 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Team Shots - Photo and Negatives; 1980's-2000's, 200951 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Coaches - Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200950 (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Negative of Field and Stadium; 1980's-2000's, 200949 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Opening pitch shot - Mounted Photo; 1980's-2000's, 200948 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Men's Basketball, 1941-2000s, 200904
      - Individual Shots- Photos; 1941-42, 200946 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Team Shots- Photos; 1955, 200945 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Individual Shots - Photos; pre 1970's, 200944 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Headshots- Photos; 1978-79, 200943 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Rice vs. Baylor- Photos; 1979, 200942 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Individual and Games Shots; 1979, 200941 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Rice vs. Texas- Photos; late 1970's-early 1980's, 200940 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Individual Shots- Photos; late 1970's- early 1980's, 200939 (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Individual Shots; 1970's-1980's, 200938 (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - Team Photo; pre 1980's, 200937 (Box 76, Folder 26)
      - Individual Shots- Photos; pre 1990's, 200936 (Box 76, Folder 27)
      - Team and Individual Shots- Photos; 1991-1992, 200935 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - Individual Shots- Negatives; 1992, 200934 (Box 76, Folder 29)
      - Team Photo (x 2); 1994-95, 200933 (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - Game and Individual Shots- Photos; 1970's-2000's, 200932 (Box 76, Folder 31-33)
      - Games and Individual Shots- Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200931 (Box 76, Folder 34)
      - Rice Players at Children's Hospital- Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200930 (Box 76, Folder 35)
      - Team USA Player and Coach-Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200929 (Box 76, Folder 36)
      - Team Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200928 (Box 76, Folder 37-39)
      - Coach Pictures; 1980's-2000's, 200927 (Box 76, Folder 40)
      - Players and Games- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200926 (Box 76, Folder 41)
      - Rice vs. Texas A & M - Negatives; 1999-2000, 200925 (Box 76, Folder 42)
      - Rice vs. Fresno- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200924 (Box 76, Folder 43)
      - Rice vs. Navy- Negatives; 1990-2000, 200923 (Box 76, Folder 44)
      - Rice vs. SMU- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200922 (Box 76, Folder 45)
      - Rice vs. Tulsa- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200921 (Box 76, Folder 46)
      - Individual Rice Mug Shots- Photos; 2000-01, 200920 (Box 76, Folder 47)
      - Rice vs. Fresno- Photos; 2000-01, 200919 (Box 76, Folder 48-49)
      - Rice vs. Navy- Photos; 2000-01, 200918 (Box 76, Folder 50-51)
      - Rice vs. Pan America- Photos; 2000-01, 200917 (Box 76, Folder 52-53)
      - Rice vs. SMU- Photos; 2000-01, 200916 (Box 76, Folder 54-55)
      - Rice vs. TCU- Photos; 2000-01, 200915 (Box 76, Folder 56-58)
      - Rice vs. Texas A & M- Photos; 2000-01, 200914 (Box 76, Folder 59-61)
      - Rice vs. Tulsa- Photos; 2000-01, 200913 (Box 76, Folder 62-65)
      - Rice vs. Tulsa- Photos; 2000-01, 200912 (Box 76, Folder 62-65)
      - Rice vs. U of H- Photos; 2000-01, 200911 (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
      - Rice vs. UNLV- Photos; 2000-01, 200910 (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
      - Players at Children's Hospital- Photos; 2000-01, 200909 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Coach Shots (Games and Family)- Photos; 2000-01, 200908 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Cheerleaders, Shots of Autry Court and Misc. Photos; 2000-01, 200907 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Group and Team- Photos; various years, 200906 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Rice Players to go Professional (Kleine, Lohaus, Buechler)-Photos; 1970's-2000's, 200905 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Women's Basketball, 1970s-2000s, 200890
      - Game and Action Shots- Photos; 1980, 200903 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Games Shots- Photos; 1986, 200902 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Coach Mike Dunavant- Photo; 1970's, 200901 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Rice vs. Illinois State- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200900 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Rice vs. Tulsa- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200899 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Rice vs. Colorado State University (CSU)- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200898 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Rice vs. Miami - Negatives; 1999-2000, 200897 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Rice vs. SMU- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Rice vs. Texas Tech- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200895 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Rice vs. Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University ( FAMU); 1999-2000, 200894 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Hackerman Invitational- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200893 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Team Pictures and Headshots- Photos + Negatives; 1980's-2000's, 200892 (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Team Pictures and Headshots- Photos + Negatives; 1980's-2000's, 200891 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Men's and Women's Basketball, 1999-2000, 200888
      - Men vs. Navy and Women vs. Illinois State- Negatives; 1999-2000, 200889 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Cross Country, 1980s-2000s, 200886
      - Meet Photos; 1980's-2000's, 200887 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Sub-subseries 6: Football, 1912-2000s, 200781
      - Team Photos; 1912, 200885 (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - Team Photos; 1914, 200884 (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Team Photos; 1915, 200883 (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Team Photos; 1916, 200882 (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Team Photos; 1917, 200881 (Box 77, Folder 29)
      - Team Photos; 1918, 200880 (Box 77, Folder 30)
      - Team Photos; 1919, 200879 (Box 77, Folder 31)
      - Team Photos; 1921, 200878 (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - Team Photos; 1922, 200877 (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1922, 200876 (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1923, 200875 (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1924, 200874 (Box 77, Folder 37)
      - Team Photos; 1926, 200873 (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - Individuals- Photos; early 1930's, 200872 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1935, 200871 (Box 77, Folder 40)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1936, 200870 (Box 77, Folder 41)
      - Team Photos; 1937, 200869 (Box 77, Folder 42)
      - Team Photos; 1941, 200868 (Box 77, Folder 43)
      - Team Photos; 1942, 200867 (Box 77, Folder 44)
      - Individuals-Photos; 1944, 200866 (Box 77, Folder 45)
      - Team Photos; 1944, 200865 (Box 77, Folder 46)
      - Glass Sheet with Photo-Player #38 Humble; 1946, 200864 (Box 77, Folder 47)
      - Team Photos; 1946, 200863 (Box 77, Folder 48)
      - Game Photos; 1946, 200862 (Box 77, Folder 49)
      - Team Photos; 1946-47, 200861 (Box 77, Folder 50)
      - Team Photos; 1947, 200860 (Box 77, Folder 51)
      - Team Photos; 1949, 200859 (Box 77, Folder 52)
      - Game Photos; 1949, 200858 (Box 77, Folder 53)
      - Individuals (Guy Warrell and Ted Schruggs)- Photos; 1946-1950, 200857 (Box 77, Folder 54)
      - Team Photos; 1950, 200856 (Box 77, Folder 55)
      - Individuals- Photos; 1950, 200855 (Box 77, Folder 56)
      - Team Photos; 1951, 200854 (Box 77, Folder 57)
      - Individuals (K. Johnson and M. Micho)-Photos; 1951- early 50's, 200853 (Box 77, Folder 58)
      - Team Photos; 1952, 200852 (Box 77, Folder 59)
      - Team Photos; 1953, 200851 (Box 77, Folder 60)
      - Team Photos; 1954, 200850 (Box 77, Folder 61)
      - Individuals- Photos; 1955, 200849 (Box 77, Folder 62)
      - Team Photos; 1955, 200848 (Box 77, Folder 63)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1955, 200847 (Box 77, Folder 64)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1956, 200846 (Box 77, Folder 65)
      - Game Photos; 1956, 200845 (Box 77, Folder 66)
      - Group and Team Photos; 1957, 200844 (Box 77, Folder 67)
      - Team Photos; 1957, 200843 (Box 77, Folder 68)
      - Game Photos; 1958, 200842 (Box 77, Folder 69)
      - Individuals- Photos; 1920's-1950's, 200841 (Box 77, Folder 70)
      - Individuals- Photos; 1960, 200840 (Box 77, Folder 71)
      - Individuals- Photos; 1961, 200839 (Box 77, Folder 72)